NUMAZU FIRST GENERAL HOSPITAL
（沼津第一綜合醫院）
But I've got an appointment with Dr. Hayami at 5 p.m.
但我…我跟速水醫師 約了下午五點見面
He told me it was an urgent operation.
醫師說那個手術很緊急
Did he?
這樣啊…
Would you know when it finishes?
那妳知道手術會什麼時候完成嗎？
Oh, ma'am, what's the matter?
奶奶，怎麼了？
I'm sorry, I have not been feeling well since this morning,
不好意思，我早上開始就覺得不舒服
and I don't know which department to go to.
但我不知道該去看哪科
LINEUP OF MODELS HANDLING CABRERA SEQUENCE
（處理卡布雷拉序列的型號陣容）
The biggest difference between this and past models
它跟以前的型號最大的分別是
is the improvement in controllability and…
更加容易操作，還有…
great improvement in the accuracy in data analysis.
在資料分析精確度方面…
What are you doing on your own?
你自己一個在做什麼？
-Oh. I'm practicing. -Practicing?
-練習 -練習？
I have to persuade him to sign the contract today.
今天我一定要讓醫師在合約上簽名
But Dr. Hayami has left already.
但速水醫師已經回家了
What? But the receptionist said that he had an urgent operation.
什麼？但剛才她說醫師 要做一個緊急的手術…
He got away again.
又讓他逃掉了
Seriously?
不是吧？
I'm sorry.
啊…對不起
It's okay.
沒關係
Well, I can't tell you that.
你問我也沒用
Yeah, I guess…
也對喔…
Hey, hey, hey… Segawa.
喂…小瀨川
Oh, Mr. Ishida! Glad to see you here.
石田先生，承蒙你照顧了
Don't tell me that you were… beaten today as well.
難不成你今天也…被擊沉了？
Yes, I was…
是的
Let's have a strategy meeting. I've found a nice conference room.
去開作戰會議吧？ 我找到一間蠻好的會議室
Of course. Please let me join the meeting.
好的，請讓我也一起去
HOSTESS BAR
（女招待酒吧）
I've told you,
我說過了
that Dr. Hayami does whatever I tell him to where salespeople are concerned.
製造商方面，速水醫師全都聽我的
It's the timing. I am still waiting for the perfect time.
是時機啦，我在等待時機
Please help me with that.
那拜託您了
Okay! Let's go to the next one.
好，去下一家吧
The bill, please!
結帳
There you go.
你的帳單
MR. SEGAWA
（瀨川先生）
290,000 yen!
29萬？
Would you like to pay in cash or by card?
請問是用現金還是信用卡付錢？
But the whiskey-and-water and the fried chicken…
但兌了水的威士忌和炸雞…
Hello.
這位客人
Is there a problem with your bill?
帳單哪裡有問題？
Well, you have to list the items on the bill…
那個…你有義務在帳單上列出明細…
Too close…
太近了…
Yes?
什麼？
Are you Who Are You's Aihara?
你是風愛友的相原嗎？
Seriously?
真的假的？
I'm honored!
真光榮
It never occurred to me that I would meet the legendary Kiichi Aihara.
我們竟然能見到 傳說中最厲害的相原希一大人
The weakest guy ever.
是傳說中沒用得最厲害
Really? 100 to six? You're so stupid!
一百個人對六個人 這事是真的嗎？好笨喔
It was 100 to five. Because Mr. Aihara ran away.
是100對5，因為相原逃了
I thought you went to Tokyo.
你不是去東京了嗎？
I came back last month because I was transferred.
我上個月被公司調回來了
So have you met the guys?
那你去見他們了嗎？
No, not yet.
不…還沒
Well, of course.
我想也是
You wouldn't dare to meet them.
你怎麼有臉去見他們？
If you ask why I say he's stupid, it's because at that time,
說他們笨是為什麼呢？那時候他們啊
when those guys were being punched, and if he had come…
被我打得豬頭似的 如果這傢伙來了…
Excuse me!
不好意思
Hey! Stop struggling!
喂，別一直動
Hey!
妳夠了沒？
Drive the car here.
把車開來
Okay…
-是
We're done here. Go home.
走吧，沒你的事了，回去吧
-But the money… -This is Tagawa.
但那些錢…
You're nothing but trouble.
真是，總給我們添麻煩
Please have this.
請用
I'm exhausted.
累死了
Hey! Go now.
喂，快走
It's getting colder.
之後還會一直這麼冷吧
GOOD AT FIGHTING; THE MOST TERRIFYING LEGEND
（打架超強，最恐怖傳說）
-You! Search here! -Okay.
-你們去找那邊 -是
-Find her even if you have to die! -Okay…
-死也要給我找出來！
Is she in the men's toilet?
她是在男廁嗎？
Yes, I think she is.
是，我想她應該在
Oh? It's you, wimp?
什麼？是沒用鬼啊？
Hello.
你好
Did you see the kid in our office just now?
有看到剛剛在事務所的小鬼嗎？
Yes? But just now…
什麼？但剛才…
-Why did you let her bite you? -I'm sorry!
-居然被她咬？你是怎樣？ -對不起
Bring her to our office if you see her, got it?
看到了就帶來事務所，聽到了嗎？
Okay.
是
-Get away! It's your fault, idiot! -I'm sorry!
-走開，都是你的錯，混蛋 -對不起
Anyway, they'll do something to help you if you go there.
總之妳先去那裡 他們會有辦法幫妳的
Bye.
我走了
MARUTAKA STORE
（丸高商店）
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
Hello.
你好
-Are you together? -Together?
-這些一起付費嗎？ -一起？
Will you stop that? Don't get attached to me.
夠了吧，別再跟著我
I know it's uncool for me to say it,
我知道說出來很遜
but I really don't want to have anything to do with the gangsters.
但我真的不想和黑社會扯上關係
Our company is fussy about obeying rules and stuff…
我公司對守規矩這件事情很囉嗦
What on earth am I saying?
我到底在說什麼？
Oh, officer…
警察先生…
Hey, you…
喂，妳…
Hey.
喂…
I'll put your change of clothes here.
我把衣服放在這裡
It's really only for tonight.
真的只有一晚而已喔
You have to go first thing tomorrow morning.
妳明天一早就得回家
You ran away from home, didn't you?
妳是離家出走吧？
That's why you don't want to go to the police.
所以才討厭警察吧？
Well, I get it though.
其實我也懂
When I ran away from home, I kept getting away from
我以前離家出走
the cops… well, police officers as well.
也常躲著警察的
But why are the gangsters looking for you?
但話說回來，黑社會怎麼會抓妳？
Oh, you're that, right?
對了，妳是那個吧？
Like your parents are gangster bosses?
父母是黑社會幹部之類的
Seriously?
真的假的？
That's why the mob soldiers are frantically looking for you.
所以那些小角色才那麼拼命找
Hang on… Are you done?
等等…妳要出來了嗎？
Grandma.
奶奶
Have you phoned home?
打電話回家了嗎？
Your parents must be worried.
妳父母會擔心的
How many hundred hours will it take you to find
要找個沒錢也跑不遠的小鬼
a kid with no money who can't run far?
你們到底要花幾百個小時？
-I'm sorry!
-對不起
Get the kid here now!
-快給我帶那小鬼來！ -是
Hurry… Let's go.
快點…走了
SHE IS EMACIATED, WITH PHYSICAL SCARS…
（身體衰弱，有外傷…）
Make sure you go home, okay?
記得要回家喔，知道嗎？
This is my key.
這是鑰匙
Put it in the mailbox outside.
我放在外面的信箱
It's not much,
拿去，雖然錢不多
but it's for your travel expenses, and to buy some food if you're hungry.
妳用來坐車和買點東西吃吧
What is your name?
妳叫什麼名字？
Okay…
好吧
I'd like at least to hear your voice before we say goodbye.
我還希望臨別時能聽聽妳的聲音
Never mind.
算了
Bye.
我走了
Thank you.
謝謝
Yes?
什麼？
Bye.
再見
URARA KARAOKE BOX
（KTV麗）
Hello, ladies!
我進來了
-Manager! -Manager, it's mine.
店長
There you go.
給妳
Heard the way he said that? He's so cute!
他說“給你”，好可愛
Sit here, Manager.
店長，坐吧
-Manager, come here. -There? Okay.
-坐那邊嗎？ -這裡有空位子
Thank you, ladies.
不好意思
Manager, open your mouth.
店長，張開口
He's so cute!
好可愛
Manager, I want to sit in your lap.
店長，我想坐你的膝蓋
Come sit in my lap.
過來坐我膝蓋吧
Darn! Those stupid women… I'm not there to entertain them.
可惡！那些女人…我又不是牛郎
It's a coupon for an extended hour's free service. Please take one.
附一小時免費延長券，請參考看看
Thanks.
謝謝
It's a coupon for an extended hour's free service.
附一小時免費延長券
Keebou!
希少！
Choco…
巧克力
You should have called if you have come back, Keebou.
什麼嘛，希少 回來了至少聯絡一下我們啊
When was it?
什麼時候回來的？
A month ago. I was transferred to the office here.
一個月前，我調到這邊的營業所來
Living in your old home?
住老家嗎？
No, I live alone.
不，我自己在外面住
Where do you live?
住哪邊？
It's opposite Sakurabashi,
在櫻橋對面
the apartment where our senior, Tacchan used to live.
以前阿達前輩住的公寓
What? It's close to mine.
什麼嘛，那很近啊
Anyway, have a seat.
先坐一下吧
Let's have a gathering tonight, then.
那…今晚出來喝一杯吧
No, thanks…
不用了
Are you still bothered by that incident?
你該不會還在在意吧？
This is absurd, Keebou. It was ages ago!
你也太傻了吧，希少 那是幾年前了？
It has been ten years since…
已經十年了啊？
It was just some kids' game. No one worries about it anymore.
那只是小孩的遊戲而已 大家都不介意了
Is that why you didn't call?
你是因為這個所以沒聯絡我們嗎？
Do you meet very often?
你們常約嗎？
Well, sometimes. Not as often as before. All of us have to work.
偶爾吧，不可能像以前那樣了 大家都要工作
Choco, you're a manager?
巧克力，你當上店長了？
Yeah. The place took me on.
對，他們正式雇用了我
I'm doing a job that isn't suitable for me.
我在幹不合適的工作
I think it suits you pretty well.
不會啊，這蠻適合你的
Hey! I don't want it to.
喂，我可不想適合
What about you?
希少你呢？
I'm a salesperson. I work for a medical instrument manufacturer.
在當醫療器材製造商的推銷員
I knew university graduates were different.
大學畢業生果然不同
I say…
我說…
There you are, Manager! We have been waiting for you!
找到你了，店長，我們都在等你啦
-You're too late… -I'm coming.
-太久了吧… -我現在就去
I have to go now. I've got to go to visit my clients.
我也該走了，要去客人那裡
But it's a Saturday.
今天是星期六啊
That means nothing to a salesperson.
對推銷員來說都一樣
Bye.
走了
Hello.
妳們好
Hold on!
等一下
This is our new staff, Keebou! Go!
這是我們的新人希少，去吧！
Choco!
巧克力
Enjoy your time!
慢慢玩啊！
The sky is so gloomy.
這天還真黑…
Who are you?
你是誰？
MIKI TIRES
（三木腳踏車）
Hey! I have to sell that.
喂，那個我要賣的
Don't click your tongue. We've got a chair over there.
你嘖什麼？那裡有椅子啊
Did you do a wheelie with this?
你踏它時抬起前輪了吧？
No, I didn't.
才沒有
You'll buy and replace the rim if you've damaged it.
弄壞了你就得付錢換了
Oh, my! You're here, Pichan?
小皮，來了嗎？
Pichan?
小皮？
Grandma, Pichan's face is more rectangular.
奶奶，小皮的臉比較四方形吧？
Where is Ponjara?
碰將在哪？
-Where is Tenten? -No one is here.
-典典呢？ -都不在
Where are you going, Grandma?
奶奶，妳要去哪裡？
-I have to pick up Kosuke. -Don't bother. I'm here.
-我要去接洸介 -不用了，我在這裡
Oh, my!
哎呀…
Glad to know that.
太好了
What are Ponjara and Tenten?
碰將和典典是什麼？
They're my friends' nicknames.
那是暱稱，我同伴的
-So uncool. -Are they?
-好土 -很土嗎？
Were they your gangster friends?
是你當暴走族時的同伴？
Well, it wasn't actually a gang.
我們也不是暴走族
Do you still call each other that?
你們還那麼叫大家嗎？
Do you still call a Hotchkiss a stapler now?
你啊…現在還會把釘書機 叫成釘紙機嗎？
What is a stapler?
什麼是釘紙機？
You get what I mean.
就是那樣
I don't get it at all.
不知道你在說什麼
You can get that for 200,000 yen.
那台20萬就好
I don't want a gangster bike like this.
我才不要這暴走族機車
Biker gangs are out of date nowadays.
暴走族現在不流行了
I see.
是嗎？
Friends are annoying, right?
不煩嗎？這種同伴遊戲
You don't seem to have friends.
你啊，看起來不像有朋友
You need friends because you're weak.
太弱才會常在一起吧？ 把大家叫做同伴
Yeah. Okay, it's done.
可能是吧…好，弄好了
-Don't use it to do wheelies. -Shut up!
-別再抬起前輪了 -要你管
Good. Cheers, dude.
算不錯吧
Hey.
嘿
The big stain is totally removed.
我把那超大的污漬全除掉了
Thanks, dude.
謝謝你幫忙
Well, it's Kayo's favorite.
畢竟小佳代最愛它了
It has always been.
以前開始就是這樣
She wanted to wear it this morning, too.
她今天早上也穿這件
That's all she remembers.
她就只記得這些
Still the same?
跟以前一樣啊？
Yeah.
是啊
Just tell me if you need anything.
有什麼要幫忙的隨時告訴我
Kayo had been very nice to me.
畢竟小佳代也常常照顧我
Thanks.
謝了
By the way, Mikki.
對了，米奇
-He has come back. -Who?
-聽說他回來了 -誰？
Keebou.
希少
Choco met him by chance. He called me straight away.
巧克力偶然遇到他 然後就立刻打給我了
I see.
是嗎？
Where are you going, Grandma?
奶奶，妳要去哪裡？
What's the matter, Kayo?
小佳代，怎麼了？
Oh, my! Keebou!
哎呀，這不是希少嗎？
No… I'm Tenten. Tenten.
不是…我是典典，典典
-Tenten! -Yes.
-典典 -對…
Are you hungry, Tenten?
典典，餓了嗎？
I would love to have the curry you make again.
我好想吃小佳代的咖哩啊
Okay. Come here.
好，過來吧
You'll make it for me?
妳要弄給我吃嗎？
Let's go…
走吧…
I'm sorry.
不好意思
It's all right. Don't worry.
沒關係的，別在意
Who are you?
你是誰？
BENNY SUPERMARKET
（班尼超市）
SKELETON-SAURUS
（骷髏龍）
Hey, little boy. Stop.
嘿，小哥，停一下
How do I know if you don't talk?
你不說，我怎麼知道？
Just talk to me. I'm stupid,
說出來看看吧
Don't get so scared. It was just shoplifting,
別怕成那樣，只是在超市偷東西而已
-I… -What do you mean by that?
-我… -什麼叫“只是偷東西”？
Manager, I'm just trying to understand how young people feel.
店長，我是想要明白年輕人的感受…
-Have you called the police? -No, I haven't.
-報警了嗎？ -不，還沒
You have to do it at once!
立刻報警
But would you let me talk to him for a bit before that?
能在報警前讓我跟他談一下嗎？
Maybe he was bullied to do it.
可能他是被霸凌
What? You think you're a counselor?
什麼？你要當輔導員嗎？
I don't expect that from you.
我可沒要你做這種事啊
I see.
這樣啊…
Please! I promise I won't do this again!
求求你，我絕對不會再犯了
Please! Just don't call the police!
求求你，別報警
You see?
你知道嗎？偷東西就是盜竊 是犯罪，懂嗎？
-Come on! Call the police now! -Okay…
-好了，快報警 -是
Please! Please! Just don't call the police…
求求你…別報警
This is Benny Corporation.
是班尼公司
The Juvenile Division, please.
請轉接少年科
Yes. For shoplifting.
是，店內盜竊
Who are you?
你是誰？
Pichan!
小皮
Oh, Mr. Akagi? Long time no see.
什麼？是赤城先生，好久不見了
-Are you doing your job? -Yes.
-有好好工作嗎？ -有
I know you must be tired, but please let us see the cargo bed.
我知道你很累，不好意思 但能讓我們看看貨櫃嗎？
-Okay. -Thanks.
-好的 -謝了
Go.
去
Please have a look.
請看
What has happened?
發生什麼事了？
Kidnapping.
綁架
A ten-year-old girl.
十歲的女孩
Really? It's serious, isn't it?
真的假的？這案件很嚴重啊
You married a young, pretty lady,
你啊，娶了個年輕貌美的太太
so I thought maybe you liked little girls.
我就想你會不會是戀童癖
Don't joke about this!
別那麼說好不好？
I have to suspect everyone in my job. Sorry about that.
我的工作就是什麼都要懷疑 對不起了
I'll do anything to help, because it's you.
你要我做什麼，我都會幫忙的
The guys seem to be working hard.
他們好像也很努力
Yes.
對
I'm happy, too.
我也很高興
It's all thanks to you.
這都是多虧赤城先生您啊，好痛
Sorry about that.
不好意思了
-Sorry for causing you the trouble. -It's all right.
-對不起，給你添麻煩了 -不要緊
Let's go out for a meal some time. Ask the guys, too.
晚一點約他們一起去吃飯吧
-Sure. -Okay.
-好的 -謝謝
By the way, have you heard? He has come back.
對了，你聽說了嗎？他好像回來了
Who?
誰？
Kiichi Aihara.
相原希一
Dr. Hayami, have you read our leaflet?
醫師，請問您看過宣傳冊了嗎？
If you would call my mobile,
如果您打電話到我手機的話
I could explain it to you at any time.
我什麼時候都樂意為您解說
And… this…
還有，這個
We've made another…
請再拿去參考一下…
Okay.
是
Thank you very much!
請您多多關照
Hello.
辛苦了
Did the executive office's Mr. Ishida say something?
不知道是不是 秘書處石田先生說了什麼
Dr. Hayami took the leaflet today.
醫師今天收下了小冊子
Dr. Hayami does not know Mr. Ishida at all.
速水醫師根本完全不認識石田先生
What?
什麼？
Your neck.
印上去了
A hickey.
吻痕
What?
什麼？
Mom? What's the matter?
媽？怎麼了？
Yes? Now?
現在嗎？
Okay.
知道了
I wonder if she has gone home.
不知道她回家了沒？
HAYASHIDA CLEANING
（林田洗衣店）
Thank you, Noriaki.
典明，辛苦了
Sorry for taking up so much time, Mom.
媽，對不起，去了那麼久
-It's okay. -Please take this.
-沒關係 -這個麻煩妳
You're late!
怎麼搞的？去了那麼久
Don't come out. You have to take good care of yourself now.
別出來，現在要很小心才行
Mr. Kogure in Nakamachi needs this urgently.
中町的小暮先生說趕著要
Okay.
知道了
The two of them just kicked me really hard.
兩個孩子一起很用力地踢我
Oh, come on!
真是的
Come.
-來 -咦？好
Indeed. They're energetic.
真的，孩子都很有活力
We will meet them soon.
很快就見到孩子了
Mr. Kogure in Nakamachi, right?
中町的小暮先生，對吧？
-Thanks. -Okay.
-拜託你了 -好的
I see…
是這樣嗎？
Well, no news means good news.
不過沒有消息就是好消息了
You're staying for supper, aren't you?
你會留下吃晚飯吧？
Shall we order sushi?
我們買壽司吃吧
Please don't bother. I have to work later, sorry.
不用了，我還要工作，不好意思
I see. That must be tough for you.
是嗎？那真辛苦你了
Well, it's a good thing that you are busy.
不過忙碌也是好事
-Do you eat properly? -Yeah.
-有好好吃飯嗎？ -有
If you like,
如果你願意
you can move here at any time you want.
隨時可以搬來住
Thank you.
謝謝你
Yuta used to like you, too.
而且優太以前也很黏你
Where is Yuta? Is he at school?
優太呢？在學校嗎？
Yuta? It's me, Kiichi.
優太？是我，希一
Sorry for not keeping in touch.
對不起，我完全沒跟你聯絡
We haven't met for… three years?
三年左右沒見了吧？
I heard you weren't attending school. What's happened?
優太，我聽說你沒去上學，怎麼了？
Mr. Segawa…
瀨川先生…
I mean, your father is worried, too.
爸爸也很擔心你
I'll listen if you want to talk.
你願意的話，可以跟我說
Well, I used to skip school often, too,
不過我以前也常翹課
so I can't talk down to you.
也不能教訓你啦
But…
不過，就是…
It's all your fault!
都是你的錯！
What?
什麼？
It's your fault that I…
都是因為你，我…
They say my older brother is a legendary wimp.
他們都說我哥是傳說的沒用鬼
And he left his injured friends and ran away.
背叛了被打得很慘的同伴，自己跑了
It's your fault that people make me a laughing stock, too!
都是因為你，連我也被人拿來當笑柄
They call me the Wimp's little brother.
說我是沒用鬼的弟弟
Mikki?
米奇？
Mikki…
米奇…
Darn that stupid kid!
那臭小鬼！
Hey, little girl!
喂，小妹妹
No, they're not the girl.
-那個呢？ -這個不是
-Let's go there. -Okay.
-去那邊吧 -好的
No.
不是
Let's check that just in case.
-順便去那邊看看吧 -好吧
-Shima! -What?
-志摩先生 -什麼？
What?
什麼？
Oh?
怎麼…
Hey! I told you to go home.
喂，我不是叫妳回家了嗎？
She's not here?
不在嗎？
Hey.
喂…
What are you doing here?
妳在做什麼？怎麼躲在這裡面？
Because you didn't go home.
因為妳沒回家的事
And your stomach just rumbled?
怎麼了？妳肚子餓到咕咕叫？
Where did you find it?
這是在哪兒找到的？
It was found in the men's toilet in Hiyoko Park.
是小雞公園的男廁
What?
你說什麼？
How dare that wimp underestimate me?
那沒用鬼竟然小看我？
Sorry to have kept you waiting. Oh?
讓妳久等了…跑哪去了？
Oh, come on.
搞什麼啊？
I say,
我問妳
why is someone supposed to have taken a sick leave now in Okinawa?
為什麼請了病假休息的人 現在會在沖繩？
What?
什麼？
Gross? Me?
很噁心？我嗎？
How dare you look down on your manager…
什麼？妳居然小看店長…
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
Long time no see, huh?
很久沒見了
I'm home.
我回來了
Pichan! Welcome home!
小皮，你回來了
Come! Look at this!
你過來看！
Please! Can I buy this, please?
看這個…可以買嗎？可以嗎？求求你
You just have to buy a pan.
妳不是才買了平底鍋？
But this is totally different!
這個完全不同
You don't need oil to cook with it, isn't it amazing?
它不需要油，是不是很厲害？
-Please can I click "buy"? -How much?
-可以嗎？可以買嗎？ -多少錢？
It's 19,800 yen! And it comes with a nutcracker if you buy it now!
19800日圓！
Do we actually use a nutcracker?
妳會開核桃嗎？
I can't buy it?
不能買啊…
You're right. I always buy so much useless stuff…
也對…對不起 我總買沒用的東西回家
I'm sorry that I don't even use a nutcracker.
連核桃也不開，對不起
It's okay, just buy it. I want to have walnuts anyway.
沒關係的…買吧，反正我想吃核桃
Really?
可以嗎？
Pichan! I love you!
小皮，最喜歡你了！
Hi, Kayo!
妳好嗎，小佳代？
-There you go. -Thank you.
-你的 -謝了
Cheers.
-乾杯
You don't have to work?
店裡沒問題嗎？
No, I'm off-shift now.
嗯，有人來換班了
You haven't been drinking lately?
最近都沒喝酒嗎？
I don't know when I have to drive, that's why.
我不知道什麼時候要開車啊
Your job is tough, Mikki.
辛苦你了，米奇
It's all right.
沒這回事
-Oh. -Hey!
-對了… -很好，小佳代
There you go.
給妳
Thank you.
謝謝
-I saw him, too. -Yes?
-我也遇到他了 -誰？
Keebou.
希少
-Really? -Really. Just for a moment.
-真的？ -真的，一瞬間
A moment?
一瞬間？
We passed each other by chance.
我們偶然擦身而過
On Sakurabashi.
在櫻橋那裡
-Did you talk? -No.
-你們有說什麼嗎？ -沒有
He seemed like he had something to say, though.
他倒是好像有話想說
Did he? And you ignored him?
什麼？你沒理他嗎？
Not exactly ignored…
也不是不理他
It's just…
但就是…
I was carrying Grandma on my back at that time.
我那時背著奶奶
So?
所以呢？
I thought, "Why did he come back now? Darn him."
我只是想 “他怎麼是現在回來？可惡”
I mean, we haven't met Keebou in ten years.
我們已經有十年沒見過希少了
Why did he come back now?
但為什麼偏偏…
I see.
這樣啊…
We did something unkind to him.
我這樣真的是對不起他
Maybe he thinks I am still angry about the incident ten years ago.
他應該是覺得我還介意十年前的事吧
I am still angry.
我還介意啊
Yes?
什麼？
I am still angry about that.
我還很介意
Choco?
巧克力…
Of course I am! Are you not angry?
那是當然的了，你不介意嗎？
How can you forgive that traitor? He betrayed us!
你能原諒那傢伙嗎？ 他背叛了我們啊！
Oh, I'm sorry.
對不起
I'm sorry, Kayo.
對不起，小佳代
Feel free to sing.
妳唱歌吧
You know…
那傢伙…
He seems to be in some kind of trouble now.
現在好像惹了麻煩
You remember Tagawa?
你記得田川吧？
Black Mouse's chancellor, and he was promoted to a yakuza group.
黑老鼠的總長 然後直接當上了這邊的黑道圍事
-Oh. -He came here today.
記得
And asked me whether I knew where he lived or not.
問我知不知道那傢伙住哪裡
What did you say?
那你怎麼說？
Did you… have a nightmare?
你做惡夢了嗎？
Sort of.
我做了
I had one, too.
我也做惡夢了
Did you?
是嗎？
Don't worry.
沒事的
I think it's my stuff. Someone called me just now.
應該是我的行李，他們剛聯絡我了
What?
什麼？
Aihara, I know you're here.
相原，你在吧？
Come out!
快出來
Give me the kid! Or I'll kill you! Aihara!
把小鬼交出來，不然殺了你，相原
I know you're home! Hey!
你在裡面吧？喂！
You… You didn't run away from home, right?
我說妳…不是離家出走吧？
What happened?
妳做了什麼？
Why are the gangsters after you?
為什麼黑社會要追殺妳？
I don't know…
我不知道
-Where are you parents? -I don't know.
-父母呢？ -不知道
You don't know? Who are you?
不知道？妳到底是誰？
I don't know! I can't remember!
我不知道，我想不起來
COME HAVE FUN!
（招牌店長）
Go there.
去這裡吧
My friend is there.
我朋友在這裡
He will surely help you.
他一定會幫忙的
You can go on your own, right?
妳能一個人去吧？
I can't!
不行…
Don't cry! Show me some courage.
別哭，拿出勇氣來
You can go on your own. You will win.
妳能自己去的，妳一定能贏的
Don't go to be defeated. Go to win.
不要去輸，要去贏
Listen.
聽著
Don't be defeated until you win.
在妳贏之前，千萬別輸
No matter how hard they punch you,
無論被打得多慘
as long as you don't think that you've lost,
只要不認輸
you'll just be on your way to win the battle.
妳就在勝利的途中
Until you win…
所以，在贏之前…
Don't be defeated.
千萬別輸
-Come out! -Give us the kid!
-快出來！ -快交出那小鬼！
I know you're home!
我知道你在裡面
-Are you listening? -Hey!
-聽到了嗎？ -喂！
What's the matter?
找我有事嗎？
-Get lost! -Hey, guys!
-快滾開 -喂，等一下
Get lost!
快滾
What are you doing? You're trespassing!
你們搞什麼？這是擅闖民宅
Gosh! And you haven't taken off your shoes.
竟然還不脫鞋
Give me the kid.
該死，把小鬼交出來
What kid?
什麼小鬼？
Where have you hidden the kid?
你把小鬼藏到哪裡了？
I don't know any kid.
我說了，我不知道什麼小鬼
Hey! I'm asking you where the kid is!
喂，我在問你那小鬼在哪裡
I'll call the police if you don't stop.
你瘋夠了沒？我要報警了
Hey!
喂！
It hurts! Anyway, you should brush your teeth properly.
痛死了！你還是刷一下牙比較好
-Stand up now! -Fine, I'm going with you.
-快站起來 -知道了，走就走
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
Until you win…
在贏之前…
Don't be defeated.
千萬別輸
Okay.
好
There you go.
來
I wonder what Masayoshi is having now.
不知道雅義在吃什麼
What is the best food in Singapore?
新加坡有什麼好吃的呢？
Why didn't you go with him on his business trip?
妳跟他一起去出差不就好了？
You're newly-weds after all.
你們剛結婚，不是嗎？
Masayoshi…
雅義他…
I mean your father, he told me to wait for him here.
你爸爸叫我等他
I guess…
我想…
He wants us to get along.
他希望我們好好相處吧
I mean the two of us…
我…跟透…
I don't want supper!
我不吃飯了！
Get along? Are you kidding me?
什麼好好相處？
What? Watch the road!
搞什麼？妳知道很危險嗎？
Excuse me.
那個…
NO ENTRY
（非工作人員禁止進入）
Don't go too far!
你該乖乖合作了吧！
Stand up!
站起來
Come here.
過來
Sit!
坐下
You underestimated us. How dare you?
你竟然敢小看我？
Wimp, where is the kid?
沒用鬼，小孩在哪裡？
Kid?
小孩？
It's time for the kids to poop and take a nap now.
小孩現在該去上廁所，乖乖睡覺了
Don't feign ignorance, jerk!
你別再裝傻了
I'll ask you once more.
我再問你一次
Where is the kid?
小鬼在哪裡？
I said, I don't know.
我說了，我不知道
What kid are you talking about?
什麼小鬼？
I see.
這樣啊…
-Stand up! Now! -Now!
-站起來 -快點
Choco, you said you met him?
巧克力，你說你碰過他？
You met him?
遇過那傢伙
Yeah.
是的
He ran into me.
正面碰上了
So, how was he?
他怎麼樣？
Well, he looked cheerful.
也沒怎樣，看起來不錯
-Why did he come back? -He…
-他為什麼要回來？ -那傢伙…
He said he was transferred here, but we didn't talk much.
他說是調職回來的，但我們沒談什麼
-Son of a gun. -How dare he look down on us?
-居然小看我們
How could he bring himself to meet us, seriously?
他怎會有臉見我們？真是的
That jerk, Keebou.
希少那臭小子
Guys,
你們幾個…
it was ten years ago.
那已經是十年前的事了
It can be ten years or 100 years, but this won't go away.
管它是十年還是一百年 這是不會消失的
The fact that he betrayed his friends.
我永遠記得他背叛了同伴
Ditto. That idiot.
我也是一樣，那笨蛋
Ditto. That jerk.
我也一樣，那死傢伙
Oh, well.
說的也是…
Don't force yourself, wimp.
別硬撐了，沒用鬼
You betrayed your friends ten years ago and turned tail, didn't you?
你啊，十年前背叛了同伴 還夾著尾巴逃了，不是嗎？
Don't try to show us your courage.
你就別逞強了
Don't get too carried away, wimp!
別得寸進尺，沒用鬼
Don't underestimate us!
別小看我們！
If he had come at that time,
如果他那時來了
we wouldn't have been defeated.
我們就不會輸了
That's the one thing that we will never know.
這倒是很難說
It was 100 versus six.
是100對6啊
There could be 100 or 200 of them,
管他一百人還是兩百人
but we would have won if all six of us had been there.
六個人都在的話，我們就會贏
-We would have won. -We would have.
-我們會贏的 -會贏的
If Keebou had been there back then we would have won.
如果那時希少在的話，我們就贏了
He was that type of person.
他的確就是那樣的人
That was what he meant to us.
對我們來說
Say it, idiot!
你快說出來！
Hey, wimp!
喂，沒用鬼
It's time to give yourself a break.
別讓自己那麼痛苦了，好嗎？
Where did you hide the kid?
你把小鬼藏到哪裡了？
-I said, I don't know. -Mr. Tagawa, why have you been
我說了，我不知道
What are you, an idiot?
你這笨蛋
I told you back in the office!
我在事務所說過了，不是嗎？
Well, I was half-way through it.
雖然只說了一半
This legendary wimp…
這傳說中的沒用鬼大人
10 years ago,
在十年前
our team and his team were under the same union.
我們那隊跟他們那隊 都是同一聯盟底下的組織
We were the biggest,
我們是最大的
and those guys were the smallest, with only six people.
但相反，他們是最小的，只有六個人
There were only six of them, but they were seriously strong.
雖然是六個人 但他們打起來都很不得了
We had a really hard time fighting them.
我們要跟他們打會很辛苦
Our group had been dealing with the gangster problem,
然後，我們這組負責圍事的
and we started to join force with the union.
開始和聯盟那邊合作
When the gangsters started distributing drugs in the union
黑社會開始向聯盟提供毒品時
Keebou was the first to lead us to fight the leaders.
首先帶著我們向上層對抗的就是希少
Those guys started to tell off the guys who touched the drugs.
這傢伙就開始教訓碰了毒品的傢伙
He said he would make them take responsibility if they did it again.
說是如果他們再敢亂來 就會好好教訓他們
Even when he was threatened by the leaders, too…
就連是威脅那些幹部的時候
He actually said something cool, like, "I will draw the line myself."
還說了像“我才要跟你們劃清界線” 這麼酷的話
Didn't you, wimp?
對吧，沒用鬼？
When we called your group out to fight, only you fled.
到真的叫你們出來打了 居然就你一個臨陣退縮
If we had won that time,
如果我們那次贏了
things would definitely have been different.
事情肯定就會不同了
Many people in the union
畢竟
were seriously beaten up because of the drug incident.
聯盟那些傢伙有很多都被打得很慘
Darn!
你這該死的！
Why?
為什麼？
Why did he run away at the last moment?
為什麼到了最後關頭 他居然逃跑了？
He almost picked the fight himself, and yet…
明明就是他一個人去挑釁他們的
he forced it onto us.
卻要我們幫他收拾殘局
He had an exam.
他要考大學
What?
什麼？
The day of our fight was on the same day as his university entry exams.
打架那天和大學入學考試是同一天
What the heck?
你說什麼？
He had to take the exam at that time.
他那時候一定要去考試
What do you mean?
為什麼這麼說？
His mother was his only family.
他家裡只有他和他媽，對吧？
His mother's boyfriend back then
他媽媽的男朋友
was a high-ranking civil servant.
是蠻高階的公務員
She didn't want him to know that her son was a gangster
她不想被他知道 自己兒子是地區有名的小混混
so his mother lied to the guy.
所以他媽媽向那男人撒了謊
She told him that her son was an honest student.
說她兒子是個認真的學生
But when the guy proposed to his mother,
但當那男人向希少他媽求婚
his mother knew that the guy would know that she lied,
她知道這謊話再瞞不下去了
so she was going to reject him.
所以打算拒絕
Then…
然後希少他…
Keebou said that if he really passed the university entry exam,
說如果他真的大學合格了
then what his mother said would not be a lie.
那他媽媽就沒有說謊了
That's why Keebou studied very hard.
所以希少拼了命地唸書
All the time… Alone.
一直自己一個在唸書
So that his mother's lie would come true
就為了把媽媽的謊話變成真
and she could get married with dignity.
讓她無愧地結婚
How did you know that?
為什麼你會知道？
A while later
是沒過多久之後
Keebou's mother told my grandma.
希少媽媽告訴奶奶的
-Why didn't you tell… -I was really upset, too!
-那你為什麼之前… -我也很生氣啊！
I heard it
我聽奶奶說了
and thought he was an idiot to put his mom before his friends.
覺得他不該重視他媽多過我們 覺得他很老套
But…
不過…
I can now relate to that.
我現在總算明白了
I understand how he felt.
他那時候的心情
It's stupid to carry a burden on the shoulder.
背負著包袱本來就很老套
It's too heavy and you can't fly.
太重了，想飛也飛不起來
But…
可是…
Everybody has to bear a burden on their shoulder at some point.
每個人總有一天都要背負包袱的
Only kids can have nothing on their back.
只有小孩的背可以不用背負任何東西
I didn't have anything on my shoulder at that time.
那時我背上什麼都沒有
He was the only one…
是他自己一個人先…
to have a burden to carry first.
有了一個包袱
I understand it now.
我現在懂了
He was the one who was in pain.
痛苦的其實是他
Why, then…
那為什麼…
Why didn't he tell us?
為什麼他沒告訴我們？
That means he didn't trust us.
那代表他不相信我們啊
He said we were friends, but it meant nothing.
只是口裡說我們是朋友
In the end he didn't show up after that and went straight to Tokyo,
結果，之後他拋下了我們 就這樣去了東京
then that was it.
然後就音訊全無了
That's who he is.
正因為他是這樣的人
That's why he got into trouble with the gangsters.
所以才會惹上黑道吧？
He got into trouble with gangsters?
惹上黑道？
I don't know much.
我也不清楚
I heard that he was hiding a girl who was wanted by the gangsters.
他好像藏了個 黑道在找的女孩之類的樣子
This is funny.
好笑吧？
He made an enemy of the gangsters.
居然與黑道為敵
Choco, you…
巧克力，你…
You sold out a guy who made an enemy of the gangsters to protect a kid?
你出賣了一個 為了保護小孩與黑道為敵的人？
What do you mean by sold out?
你說什麼出賣？
They asked me, so I told them.
他問我，我才答的
That's why he couldn't tell us.
所以他才不能說啊…
-It's because we're all scum! -What?
-因為我們都是人渣！ -什麼？
You said we were friends,
還說我們是朋友
but only you do everything to protect yourself.
結果你別說壞事了 就是一起做件好事也怕
Okay, let's hold our hands and don't let go.
好，我們牽著手手，別放開喔
Don't ever let go and we'll watch each other's back!
記得別放開，要小心大家
-What the heck, Mikki? -Stop it!
-你說什麼，米奇？ -別打了！
Stop that, both of you.
你們兩個別吵了
You…
你…
-Help! -Yes?
-幫幫我 -什麼？
Help!
幫幫我
This girl is…
奇怪？這孩子…
She said she wants to come here.
她說她想來這裡
Please!
求求你們！
Help me.
幫幫我
They brought the gentleman away.
大哥哥被帶走了
Is this girl the one Keebou has been hiding?
這孩子應該就是希少 藏起來的那個孩子吧？
He told me his friend was here.
他說他朋友在這裡
He said that his friend would surely help me.
說一定會幫助我的
LET'S ALL SING TOGETHER KARAOKE BOX URARA
（一起來唱歌！KTV麗）
He told me not to be defeated…
他叫我不要輸
Not to be defeated until I win.
在贏之前千萬不要輸
It has to be Keebou.
不會錯的，那是希少會說的話
What was that?
什麼？
It's what Keebou used to say before he fought.
這是希少在打架前一定會說的話
You said that…
你們說過…
we wouldn't have been defeated if Keebou were there.
希少在的話，我們就不會輸了
I think so, too.
我也是這樣想的
Because he never admits defeat.
因為他絕對不會認輸
No matter how beaten up he was,
無論被打得多慘
he would say that we were going to win if we didn't admit defeat.
他都會說 “只要我們不認輸，那遲早會贏”
At that time…
那時候
The reason we lost wasn't because Keebou wasn't there.
我們會輸，不是因為希少不在
It was because we admitted defeat.
而是因為我們認輸了
Grandma, please take care of her.
奶奶，請妳照顧她
Hang on, Mikki.
等等，米奇
It's not a good idea to fight with gangsters.
黑道太危險了
-I was wrong. -Yes?
-我錯了 -什麼？
Someone can still fly
有人就算是背負著包袱
when they're bearing a burden.
還是能飛的
Somehow…
怎麼我覺得…
Mikki was so cool that it was gross.
米奇帥得有點噁心？
Yeah.
是啊…
So isn't it uncool if we don't go with him now?
現在我們不跟上去的話 是不是會很遜？
-Okay, let's go then! -Let's go!
-好，那快走吧！ -走吧！
If you're fighting, I'll go with you!
要鬧事的話，我也去！
KARAOKE BOX URARA
（KTV麗，招牌店長）
Hey!
喂！
Hi, I'll drive you there.
要坐嗎？
Don't come with us.
你就別去了
Your kids will be born soon.
你孩子快出生了吧？
It's all right…
沒關係啦
It's the shutdown club that used to belong to Kadomatsu Limited, right?
是門松興業那家 關了門的俱樂部，對吧？
I pass by it along my way home, so get in.
到我家去正好順路，上車吧
What?
什麼？
I thought you wanted to fly?
不是要飛嗎？
You see…
那個…
What you guys put at my place…
你們放在我家的那些東西
If only we have them…
只要有它們…
Even we can…
就算我們也可以飛
Oh!
奇怪…
You're late, Choco.
太慢了吧，巧克力
Drive now.
快開車
-Shut up and get in the van! -Let's go!
-快上去吧 -好，走吧
Hey.
我說你啊
You should tell us now.
你該說了
Where is the kid?
那小鬼在哪裡？
I have no idea.
我不知道
Yes?
是
I'm sorry.
不好意思
He's more stubborn than I thought.
他比想像中難纏
Is he?
是嗎？
Do your best.
你們加油吧
Well, if it's necessary,
不過有必要的話…
use that.
就用那個吧
Yes, sir.
是
But if he is still not talking,
可是如果這樣他還不說的話
then maybe he really doesn't know.
說不定他真的不知道
What?
什麼？
How can you be so naïve?
你在說什麼傻話？
Why? Did you say it for old time's sake?
什麼？你是想起過去了嗎？
No, that's not what I meant.
不是…沒這樣的事
Anyway, make him tell you as soon as possible.
總之，盡快讓他說出來
After he tells you…
他說了之後
Kill him.
就殺了他
I'm so grateful that you were there to help with the surgery yesterday.
真是的，昨天的手術還好有妳幫忙
Every other nurse here is useless.
這裡的護士全部都很沒用
Dr. Hayami,
速水醫師
have you decided on the replacement of the diagnostic imaging apparatus?
關於更換影像診斷裝置的事 請問你有什麼打算？
Oh, it's time to choose a manufacturer.
對了…也該決定製造商了
What will you base the choice on?
請問你是根據什麼選擇？
Base it on?
什麼？根據？
On how well they entertain you, or…
是款待得夠不夠好，還是…
Well, I'll choose based on functions, like analytical accuracy.
那當然是器材的性能了 像是解析的精確度之類的
I think this is pretty good.
我覺得這個不錯
The one made by the manufacturer who you keep ignoring.
是醫師你總是不理的 那間製造商的產品
Stop acting, will you?
我說你，別再演了
Just tell us like the wimp you are.
沒用鬼得像個沒用鬼，快說出來
Why do you care?
你管她幹嘛？
What happens to a kid not related to you is none of your business.
一個非親非故的女孩 變成怎樣也無所謂吧？
You're the one who is putting on an act, Mr. Tagawa.
田川先生，你才是在演戲吧？
What are you saying?
你說什麼鬼話？
Mr. Tagawa.
田川先生
Those were the good old days.
那時候真的很棒，對嗎？
What?
什麼？
We kept doing stupid things and mischief,
我們幹盡了蠢事和壞事
but somehow… we had some hidden rules, hadn't we?
但怎麼說… 我們有些不成文的規矩，不是嗎？
Never betray your friends, and never harm women and children.
不會背叛朋友，不會傷害女人和小孩
The person who stuck most firmly to the rules
比誰都傻傻地守著這些規矩的
was you, wasn't it?
就是你，不是嗎？
Chancellor.
總長
I say, Aihara.
我說啊，相原
It has ended. The time when we were kids and those rules applied.
那時代已經結束了
You're right.
說的也是啊
How stupid I was.
真是的…真無聊
I studied very hard and betrayed my friends and got this in return.
我拼命讀書，背叛了同伴 換來的居然是這些
Every day I bow my head and fawn on people,
每天向人卑躬屈膝
drink the sake that I hate to drink;
喝根本不想喝的酒
I got looked down on and ignored…
被人小看和無視
How stupid!
好無聊
Ah, this is really stupid!
真的很無聊
Why is that?
到底是怎麼了？
Why is being an adult so stupid?
為什麼當大人會這麼無聊？
Why is it so darn dull? Tell me, Chancellor!
為什麼會一點也不好玩？ 你說呢，總長？
A punch like this does not hurt at all.
你這拳打下來完全不痛
When compared to the guys back then.
跟那時的傢伙比起來，一點也不痛
I wanted to go.
我很想去的
I knew this at that time!
那時我也知道
I knew I would regret it for the rest of my life.
自己會後悔一生
I knew it!
我早就知道了
It doesn't hurt when people call me a wimp or a coward.
被人說我沒用或是膽小，完全不痛苦
It's not important.
那根本沒什麼
You betrayed your friends and you alone were saved.
要背叛我同伴，自己一人得救
If I have to bear this burden for life,
如果要我一生背負這個包袱
then I'd rather be killed!
我寧願被你們殺了！
-Hey! -Sit down!
-喂！ -你快坐下！
I wanted to go! I did!
我很想去…我真的是很想去的
I wanted to get beaten up with them!
我很想跟他們一起被人打
No…
不是…
We wouldn't have been defeated if I had gone. We would have won!
我去了的話就不會輸了 我們就會贏了
This is absurd.
你說什麼傻話？
It was 100 to six.
是100對6啊
It could be 100 people or 200 people,
管他一百人還是兩百人
but we would not have been defeated if all of us had been there!
我們全都去了的話，就絕對不會輸
This is stupid.
真無聊
They said the same thing, too.
他們幾個也說過同樣的話
When they got beaten up by us,
他們一邊被我們打
they said they would have killed us in seconds if Keebou were there.
邊說要是你來了 他們幾秒鐘就能打敗我們
They were right.
那當然了
Because it's a fact.
因為那是事實
But Chancellor…
但是，總長
my daily routine is incredibly dull and boring,
雖然我每天都過得無聊透頂
but I'm not going to be defeated!
但我還不打算要輸！
I won't be defeated until I win.
在贏之前，我不會輸
They won't, either.
他們也是一樣
They have not been defeated!
他們還沒有輸
We are still…
就算是現在…
on our way to claim our victory!
我們還在勝利的途中！
Keebou!
希少
We have come to win.
我們來贏了
Who are you?
你們是誰？
I am…
我是…
myself!
我自己！
Good!
-來吧！
-Who are you? -My name is Toru.
-你是誰？ -我叫透
It's not important.
別管這個了
Don't underestimate the yakuza.
別小看黑道
I'll kill you.
小心我殺了你們
Keebou!
希少
What are you doing?
你這傢伙在幹什麼？
I saw it in a movie.
我在電影看過
If you pull the trigger now the gun will fire accidentally.
如果你現在開槍，手槍就會走火
My hand will be blown off,
我的手會被轟掉
but your whole person, even your face, will turn into a mess.
但你會連臉也變得稀巴爛
Shall we try it?
試試開槍吧
To see if it's true.
看是不是真的
I remember it now.
我想起來了
How stupidly brave you are.
你那不要命的膽量
Cheers.
謝了
Take this!
看我的！
NUMAZU FIRST GENERAL HOSPITAL
（沼津第一綜合醫院）
It hurts…
好痛…
I told you.
我不是說了
I fell down the stairs when I was worrying about my sales record.
我在煩惱業績 正在發呆的時候就滾下樓梯了
I'm telling the truth!
是真的
You've sold one.
賣了一台了
Yes?
什麼？
Dr. Hayami said that he will surely show up in the next appointment.
速水醫師說 下次你約他，他一定會出現
He'd like you to tell him about the functions.
他希望你解釋一下機器的性能
You're crying?
你在哭？
I wasn't defeated.
我沒有輸
I was on my way to claim my victory.
我是還在勝利的途中…
Sorry, I don't get what you said.
對不起，我不明白你在說什麼
It was me.
是我…
I sold you out.
是我出賣你…
To Tagawa.
給田川的
I see.
是嗎？
Thanks.
謝謝你
I wanted to get beaten up. I have always wanted that.
我一直都很想被打
Bad as you guys were at that time.
像你們那時被打得那麼慘
I was responsible for that.
這是我要負的責任
What are you, a masochist?
你是被虐狂嗎？
A university graduate does talk differently.
大學畢業生說的話果然不一樣
-Sure. -Gosh, you're infuriating.
-當然了 -你真會惹人生氣
Lost her memory?
失憶了？
She doesn't seem to remember stuff like her own name.
她好像連自己的名字也想不起來
That's why I don't get it.
所以我才搞不懂
Why are the gangsters after her?
為什麼黑道要抓她？
Where had she been and what had she done before she met me?
在遇到我之前，在哪裡做過些什麼？
We really have to ask the question, "Who are you?"
真的要問一句“你是誰？”
Who are you?
妳到底是什麼人？
Mr. Akagi!
赤城先生
What are you doing? Having a class reunion?
怎麼了？在開同學會嗎？
Long time no see, Mr. Akagi!
赤城先生，好久不見了
Hey, Ponjara.
你好嗎，碰將？
You're working hard, aren't you?
你好像很努力過活呢
Yes!
是
She's the girl?
就是她嗎？
Are you hurt?
小妹妹，沒受傷吧？
Someone in the neighborhood reported this.
附近有人通知我
-I'll take her with me. -Why?
-我要帶她走了 -什麼？
-But I… -I know.
-但是我… -我知道
You have been protecting her from the Kadomatsu Group's gangsters.
你從門松他們手上救了她
I think I'll have to ask you about the details later,
我之後要問你詳細的情形
but I'll take her back to her parents for now.
不過我現在還是先送她回家吧
I'm happy for you.
真是太好了
Come with me.
來，跟叔叔走吧
Don't worry. You can trust him.
不用怕，妳可以相信他
He was very kind to us when we were bad kids.
從我們還是壞孩子時 他就幫了我們很多忙
Let's go.
走吧
-Sorry for the interruption. -Please take care of her.
-打擾你們了 -麻煩你了
Work hard, guys.
你們要加油喔
-Sure. -We will.
-我們會的 -知道了
Mr. Akagi.
對了，赤城先生
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
What is her name?
這孩子叫什麼名字？
It's Hikari.
日花里
Hikari Goto.
五嶋日花里
What a lovely name.
很好的名字
See you, Hikari.
日花里，再見
See you, Keebou.
再見，希少
-Bye. -Thanks.
-再見 -謝謝
Stay away from that kid.
別接近那小鬼了
I'm telling you to stop.
我叫你不要去
I want to see this through.
-再插手太危險了 -自己參與過的事，我希望能做到底
You're that guy after all!
離開我們後，你果然變了
I want the truth.
我想快點知道真相
Then let's go find the truth.
-那就去確認一下吧 -希少！
Show us what you're made of!
你就繼續耍酷啊